https://www.osv.com/privacy-policy/

Updated: 9/23/2016
Our Sunday Visitor is committed to protecting your privacy and developing technology that gives you the most powerful and safe online experience. This Statement of Privacy applies to osv.com and governs data collection and usage. By using osv.com, you consent to the data practices described in this statement.
Collection of your Personal Information
Our Sunday Visitor collects personally identifiable information, such as your e-mail address, name, home or work address or telephone number. Our Sunday Visitor also collects anonymous demographic information, which is not unique to you, such as your zip code, age, gender, preferences, interests and favorites.
There is also information about your computer hardware and software that is automatically collected by Our Sunday Visitor. This information can include: your IP address, browser type, domain names, access times and referring website addresses. This information is used by Our Sunday Visitor for the operation of the service, to maintain quality of the service, and to provide general statistics regarding use of osv.com.
Please keep in mind that if you directly disclose personally identifiable information or personally sensitive data through Our Sunday Visitor public message boards, this information may be collected and used by others.
Our Sunday Visitor encourages you to review the privacy statements of websites you choose to link to from Our Sunday Visitor so that you can understand how those websites collect, use, and share your information. Our Sunday Visitor is not responsible for the privacy statements or other content on websites outside of Our Sunday Visitor’s family of websites.
Use of your Personal Information
Our Sunday Visitor collects and uses your personal information to operate osv.com and deliver the services you have requested. We keep track of the websites and pages our customers visit within Our Sunday Visitor’s family of websites in order to determine which Our Sunday Visitor products and services are the most popular. This data is used to deliver customized content and advertising within Our Sunday Visitor to customers whose behavior indicates that they are interested in a particular subject area.
Our Sunday Visitor may use your personally identifiable information to inform you of other products or services available from Our Sunday Visitor and its affiliates. We may also contact you via surveys to conduct research about your opinion of current products and services or of potential new products and services that may be offered.
Our Sunday Visitor may contact you on behalf of external business partners about a particular offering that may be of interest to you. In those cases, your unique personally identifiable information (e-mail, name, address, telephone number) is not transferred to the third party.
Our Sunday Visitor may share data with trusted partners to help us perform statistical analysis, send you email or postal mail, provide customer support, or arrange for deliveries. All such third parties are prohibited from using your personal information except to provide these services to Our Sunday Visitor, and they are required to maintain the confidentiality of your information.
Our Sunday Visitor may rent your name, address, or email address for one-time use to reputable businesses that can provide you with valuable offers and information. To opt out of receiving these third party offers, write to us by email at osvmkt@osv.com.
Our Sunday Visitor will disclose your personal information without notice only if required to do so by law or in the good faith belief that such action is necessary to: (a) conform to the edicts of the law or comply with legal process served on Our Sunday Visitor or the site; (b) protect and defend the rights or property of Our Sunday Visitor; and, (c) act under exigent circumstances to protect the personal safety of users of Our Sunday Visitor or the public.
Use of Cookies
Osv.com uses “cookies” to help you personalize your online experience. A cookie is a text file that is placed on your hard disk by a Web page server. Cookies cannot be used to run programs or deliver viruses to your computer. Cookies are uniquely assigned to you, and can only be read by a web server in the domain that issued the cookie to you.
One of the primary purposes of cookies is to provide a convenience feature to save you time. The purpose of a cookie is to tell the Web server that you have returned to a specific page. For example, if you personalize Our Sunday Visitor pages, or register with osv.com, a cookie helps Our Sunday Visitor to recall your specific information on subsequent visits. This simplifies the process of recording your personal information, such as billing addresses, shipping addresses, and so on. When you return to osv.com, the information you previously provided can be retrieved, so you can easily use the Our Sunday Visitor features that you customized.
You have the ability to accept or decline cookies. Most Web browsers automatically accept cookies, but you can usually modify your browser setting to decline cookies if you prefer. If you choose to decline cookies, you may not be able to fully experience the interactive features of the Our Sunday Visitor services or websites you visit.
Security of your Personal Information
Our Sunday Visitor secures your personal information from unauthorized access, use or disclosure. Our Sunday Visitor secures the personally identifiable information you provide on computer servers in a controlled, secure environment, protected from unauthorized access, use or disclosure. When personal information (such as a credit card number) is transmitted to other websites, it is protected through the use of encryption, such as the Secure Socket Layer (SSL) protocol.
Changes to this Statement
Our Sunday Visitor will occasionally update this Statement of Privacy to reflect company and customer feedback. Our Sunday Visitor encourages you to periodically review this Statement to be informed of how Our Sunday Visitor is protecting your information.
Contact Information
Our Sunday Visitor welcomes your comments regarding this Statement of Privacy. If you believe that Our Sunday Visitor has not adhered to this Statement, please contact Our Sunday Visitor at customerservice@osv.com. We will use commercially reasonable efforts to promptly determine and remedy the problem.
